checkfreescore.com 2016-10-25

# Get Your Free Credit Score Online Today!

7-Day Free Trial  
**Ends Nov. 1, 2016**

Monthly Membership of **$29.95**  
automatically charged after free trial

To Cancel, Just Call  
**(855) 504 5868**

##### We Are Committed to Safeguarding Customer Information 

In order to better serve your needs now and in the future, we may ask you to provide us with certain information. In order to provide the products and services you request from us, we may also obtain consumer reports and other information from consumer reporting agencies, our affiliate consumer reporting agency companies, and other data and information providers. We understand that you may be concerned about what we will do with such information - particularly any personal or financial information. We agree that you have a right to know how we will utilize such information. Therefore, we have adopted this Privacy Policy to govern the use and handling of your personal information. 

##### Applicability 

This Privacy Policy governs our use of the information that you provide to us or we otherwise obtain in providing our products and services to you. Our partner company, CSIdentity Corporation, Inc. ("CSID"), has also adopted guidelines that govern our use of personal information which can be found on CSID's website at http://www.csid.com/privacy-policy/.

##### Types of Information 

Depending upon which of our services you are utilizing, the types of nonpublic personal information that we may collect include: 

  * Information we receive from you on applications (either applications with us directly or through our clients), forms and in other communications to us, whether in writing, in person, by telephone or any other means
  * Information about your transactions with us, our affiliated companies, or others; and
  * Information we receive from a consumer reporting agency and other data and information providers.

##### Changes to Information 

If you want to update or correct information you have provided to CheckFreeScore.com, you can do so by sending us a letter to 5100 Buckeystown Pike Suite 250 Frederick, MD 21704. If you want to correct information in a consumer report we provide on you that you believe is incorrect, you can do so through the dispute resolution process provided under the Fair Credit Reporting Act or other applicable laws.   
Use of Information 

We request information from you or obtain information about you for our own legitimate business purposes and not for the benefit of any third party. Therefore, we will not release your information to any party, whether affiliated with us or not, except: (1) as necessary for us or a third party to provide the product or service you have requested; or (2) as permitted by law. We may, however, store such information, including during the period after which any customer relationship has ceased. Such information may be used for any internal purpose, such as quality control efforts or customer analysis.

##### Former Customers 

Even if you are no longer our customer, our Privacy Policy will continue to apply to you.

##### Confidentiality and Security 

We will use our best efforts to: (a) protect the confidentiality of your nonpublic personal information (including your social security number) and ensure that no unauthorized parties have access to any of your information, (b) restrict access to nonpublic personal information about you to those individuals and entities that need to know that information to provide products or services to you, and (c) prevent the unlawful disclosure of your nonpublic personal information (including your social security number). We will use our best efforts to train and oversee our employees and agents to ensure that your information will be handled responsibly and in accordance with this Privacy Policy and CSID's guidelines. We currently maintain physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards that comply with federal regulations to guard your nonpublic personal information.

We may, from time to time, contact you via e-mail to inform you of changes or updates to our site or products. We will never send you a request via e-mail for any personal information (e.g., social security number, account number, date of birth, etc.)

##### Collection / Use of Information

The Company and its affiliates may collect personally identifiable information when you specifically and knowingly provide it to us, such as when you submit your personal information such as your e-mail address, name, phone number or address when you sign up on the site.

Company will use the personally identifiable information directly submitted by you for the purposes described in this policy. We may use the information you provide to us to contact you for reasons related to your original communication to us, and we may also share your information with third party marketing partners so they may offer you products and services that you may find of interest.

We and/or our partners use cookies and web beacon technology to associate certain Internet-related information about you, such as your Internet Protocol address and what Web browser you are using, with certain of your online behaviors, such as opening emails or browsing websites. Such information is used to customize ads or content and may be shared with our partners.

Our partners may use this information to recognize you across different channels and platforms over time for advertising, analytics, attribution, and reporting purposes. For example, our partners may deliver an ad to you in your web browser based on a purchase you made in a physical retail store, or they may send a personalized marketing email to you based on the fact that you visited a particular website.

You may be contacted via telephone and/or email regarding any product that CheckFreeScore.com or Partners and/or Affiliates, or other Third Party Marketers may market from time to time.

##### Cookies

Company, or third parties on our behalf, may also collect non-personally identifiable information via the use of cookies. Cookies are pieces of information that are transferred to an individual's hard drive for record-keeping purposes. Cookies are used to assist you in using site information and content by saving your user preferences. Cookies are also used to collect aggregate information about Web site users on an anonymous basis. Company has contractual relationships with third parties, including without limitation, advertisers and companies to place online advertisements that may place their own cookies on the Web sites displaying our content. In the course of serving these advertisements, such third parties may place or recognize a unique cookie of their own on your browser, and they may or may not collect personally identifiable information. Such third parties' use of cookies will be guided by their individual privacy policy, which you should review. Company does not control such third party cookies.

The cookies may reflect demographic or other data linked to data you voluntarily have submitted to us, e.g., your email address, which we may share with a data provider solely in hashed, non-human readable form. We and/or our partners may also use cookie's for delivering personalized advertising emails. These cookies are used to identify the visitors of our advertisers' websites and to personalize content, experiences and advertisements based on the visitors' browsing experience.

Users can also express their choices for display advertising, through the following platforms: Digital Advertising Alliance opt-out platform or the Network Advertising Initiative opt-out platform.

To opt-out of these cookies, please go to <http://www.aboutads.info/choices>.

##### Communications

Company will not read, listen to or disclose to any third parties private communications that are transmitted using Company services except as required by law or in order to ensure proper operation of services.

##### Unlawful Activity

Company may use customer identifiable information to investigate and help prevent potentially unlawful activity or activities that threaten the integrity of service or network integrity or otherwise violate Company's Usage Agreement or Terms of Service.

##### Account Information

Company provides an online account for customers to update account information. The customer is responsible for ensuring that the information on file with Company is current and accurate. You may update the personal information you have provided to us, or request that your information be removed completely, at any time, by submitting an email to info@checkfreescore.com, by updating your account info by logging into your account, or by writing to us at the address listed below.

##### Children Privacy Policy

Company does not sell products or services for purchase by children. Company does not knowingly solicit or collect customer identifiable information from children or teenagers under the age of eighteen. In addition, Company will not knowingly link to any third party web site that solicits or collects customer identifiable information from minors.

##### Material Changes in Privacy Policy and Former Statements 

Any material changes to our Privacy Practices or security procedures will be posted on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect and how we use it as well as the latest material changes we make to our security procedures.

Should you have any questions about Privacy, please contact:

CheckFreeScore.com

5100 Buckeystown Pike Suite 250 Frederick, MD 21704 

_Last updated on June 10, 2016_
